https://www.judaicaspecialties.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
WELCOME TO JUDAICA SPECIALTIES!
Jewish Kidstuff & Pet Toys
Jewish Dolls ,
0
Your shopping cart is empty!
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
JudaicaSpecialties.com is committed to
protecting the privacy of our customers. Information we collect is used
solely to process orders and enhance your personal shopping experience.
Please read below for more detailed information about our privacy
policy. JudaicaSpecialties does not rent, trade or sell your personal
information to any third party.Our
site uses an order form so that you can request information, products,
and services. Contact information (email address, telephone number,
etc.) from the order form is used to send your orders and information
about our company to you. Your contact information is also used to get
in touch with you when necessary. Contact information for gift
recipients may also be collected in order to ensure correct gift
delivery. Financial information (credit card numbers, credit card
expiration dates, billing address, etc.) that is collected is used to
bill you for products and services. Financial information is not used
for any other purpose than billing.We
may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and
to administer our Web site. Your IP address can also be used to gather
broad demographic information and to recognize customer traffic patterns
and site usage. This information aids us in merchandising, and in
developing the design and layout of the site. JudaicaSpecialties
sometimes administers surveys from the web site in which we ask you for
demographic information and opinions. We do not ask you for contact
information in regards to survey data. We use the data to better
understand the needs of all our customers. We will never contact you
regarding the answers or results provided in the survey.This
site uses a secure server (SSL) to encrypt all of your personal
information. We use strong security measures to protect the loss, misuse
and alteration of your information under our control.If you wish to receive announcement or special offers from us you can: Send an email to: offers@judaicaspecialties.com or call our toll free number 888.277.7897.
By using our web site, you agree to the collection and use of this
information. We will post any changes to our Privacy Policy on this page
so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we
use it. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the
practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, please
contact us at the web site address or toll free number listed above.
